// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What TV show did Kevin work on?', 
      a: 'Law & Order SVU', 
      b: 'Breaking Bad',
      c: 'Monk',
      d: 'Enlightened',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where did Kevin and Marion meet?', 
      a: 'At Marion\'s work HH in NY', 
      b: 'Working at CH',
      c: 'On christianmingle.com',
      d: 'At Kev\'s roommate\'s bday',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What town in NJ is Kevin from?', 
      a: 'Morristown', 
      b: 'Montclair',
      c: 'Newbridge',
      d: 'Rutherford',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What sport did Kevin play extensively as a child?', 
      a: 'Soccer', 
      b: 'Football',
      c: 'Volleyball',
      d: 'Baseball',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In Kevin\'s opinion, what\'s the best slasher movie?', 
      a: 'Halloween', 
      b: 'Happy Death Day',
      c: 'The Unseen',
      d: 'Scream',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What phrase did Kev coin during a Shins concert in Coney Island in the late 2000\'s?', 
      a: 'All the things!', 
      b: 'Sports!',
      c: 'Fail!',
      d: 'Cool Story Bro!',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these was NOT one of Kevin\'s CHILDHOOD pets?', 
      a: 'Lucy', 
      b: 'Bogsy',
      c: 'Quirky',
      d: 'Bailey',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Kevin\'s great grandparents are from what country?', 
      a: 'Romania', 
      b: 'Greece',
      c: 'Armenia',
      d: 'Italy',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Kevin\'s favorite sports team of all time?', 
      a: 'Boston Red Sox', 
      b: 'New York Yankees',
      c: 'New York Mets',
      d: 'Los Angeles Dodgers',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which celebrity is sort of Kevin\'s cousin?', 
      a: 'Keira Knightley', 
      b: 'Natalie Portman',
      c: 'Alison Brie',
      d: 'Rooney Mara',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};